<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes" ?>



<title>KYBO 3.0.0</TITLE>




<item>
<title><COLOR aqua>***Sci Fy***</COLOR></title>
</item>






<item>
<title>Vice (2015)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjE4OTg3Mjg5OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzYxMTg0MzE@._V1_SX500_SY999_.jpg?</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://i.imgur.com/EAFHO8e.png</fanart>
<info>Bruce Willis stars in this Sci-Fi thriller about ultimate resort: VICE, where customers can play out their wildest fantasies with artificial inhabitants who look like humans.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Transformers Age of Extinction (2014)</title>
<link>http://144.76.186.45/r57/5/tyler/movie/TransformersAgeofExtinctionDVD-TylerMovieLand.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>http://th07.deviantart.net/fs71/PRE/f/2014/133/5/a/transformers__age_of_extinction__2014____poster_by_camw1n-d7i1moa.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://filmclassjunkies.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/transformers-4-age-of-extinction-optimus-prime-poster.jpg</fanart>
<info>After an epic battle, a great city lies in ruins, but the Earth itself is saved. As humanity begins to pick up the pieces, a shadowy group emerges to try to take control of history. Meanwhile, an ancient and powerful new menace sets its sights on Earth. A new group of humans, led by Cade Yeager (Mark Wahlberg), helps Optimus Prime (Peter Cullen) and the Autobots rise up to meet their most fearsome challenge yet: a worldwide war of good versus evil.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Dawn of the Planet of the Apes (2014)</title>
<link>http://144.76.186.45/r57/5/tyler/movie/DawnofthePlanetoftheApesDVD-TylerMovieLand.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>http://girlandboything.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/DAWNOFTHEPLANETOFTHEAPES-poster.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://www.seoulsync.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/article-julyevents-dawnoftheplanetoftheapes.jpg</fanart>
<info>Ten years after simian flu wiped out much of the world's homosapiens, genetically enhanced chimpanzee Caesar (Andy Serkis) and his ever-growing band of followers have established a thriving colony just outside San Francisco in Muir Woods. Meanwhile, a small band of human survivors emerges, which forces Caesar -- as leader -- to grapple with the dual challenge of protecting his people and re-establishing a relationship with the remaining human population -- the latter being Caesar's secret wish.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Jurassic City (2014)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://img.rlsbb.com/images/ikB81QU.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://i.ytimg.com/vi/eFxiY7Iq2RA/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
<info>When a top-secret laboratory is unexpectedly breached, thousands of rampaging raptors are unleashed on Los Angeles! A black-ops unit is mobilized to contain the creatures before they cause city-wide chaos. Simultaneously, a truckload of raptors is rerouted to a nearby prison. Upon their escape, these ferocious flesh-eaters are beyond containment. This is Jurassic judgment night for smoking hot sorority girls, sinister scientists, muscle-bound military and doomed death-row inmates! It's about to get bloody in Jurassic City!</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Edge of Tomorrow (2014)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>https://dyncdn.me/posters2/1/11178b85af533ed356c0993c1a3684d0e1474c3d.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://torrentsmovies.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/Edge-Of-Tomorrow-2014.jpg</fanart>
<info>A military officer is brought into an alien war against an extraterrestrial enemy who can reset the day and know the future. When this officer is enabled with the same power, he teams up with a Special Forces warrior to try and end the war.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Ender’s Game (2014)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>https://s3.amazonaws.com/orbitbooks/Enders-Game-film-poster.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://cdn.destructoid.com//ul/269909-enders-game-tv.jpg</fanart>
<info>Young Ender Wiggin is recruited by the International Military to lead the fight against the Formics, a genocidal alien race which nearly annihilated the human race in a previous invasion.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Earth to Echo (2014)</title>
<link>http://144.76.186.45/r57/5/tyler/movie/EarthtoEchoDVD-TylerMovieLand.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>http://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w396/tWPWo3JgwM7uGX096mWXmWPl8k8.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://i.ytimg.com/vi/1Z8R6h0br8o/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
<info>After receiving a bizarre series of encrypted messages, a group of kids embark on an adventure with an alien who needs their help.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Ghost in the Shell Arise Border 3 Ghost Tears (2014) SUB</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w396/4rMUx6aAZX1QGtMpjHakXDdhYDM.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://www.animexis.com.br/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/Ghost-In-The-Shell-Arise-characters.jpg?f41465</fanart>
<info>(ENG SUB) The anime's story is set in 2027, one year after the end of the fourth non-nuclear war. New Port City is still reeling from the war's aftermath when it suffers a bombing caused by a self-propelled mine. Then, a military member implicated in arms-dealing bribes is gunned down. During the investigation, Public Security Section's Daisuke Aramaki encounters Motoko Kusanagi, the cyborg wizard-level hacker assigned to the military's 501st Secret Unit. Batou, a man with the "eye that does not sleep," suspects that Kusanagi is the one behind the bombing. The Niihama Prefectural Police detective Togusa is pursuing his own dual cases of the shooting death and a prostitute's murder. Motoko herself is being watched by the 501st Secret Unit's head Kurutsu and cyborg agents.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Transcendence (2014)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTc1MjQ3ODAyOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjI1NDQ0MTE@._V1_SX500_SY999_.jpg?</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://queenofthenerds.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/Transcendence-Movie-Wallpaper-HD-Resrs.jpg</fanart>
<info>A scientist's drive for artificial intelligence, takes on dangerous implications when his consciousness is uploaded into one such program.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Lucy (2014)</title>
<link>http://144.76.186.45/r57/5/tyler/movie/LucyDVD-TylerMovieLand.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>http://cdn.my.churpieblogs.com/wp-content/uploads/my/2014/08/lucy-keyart-small.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://and.kz/userfiles/item/x48245d20140925174223.jpg</fanart>
<info>A woman, accidentally caught in a dark deal, turns the tables on her captors and transforms into a merciless warrior evolved beyond human logic.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>RoboCop (2014)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjAyOTUzMTcxN15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjkyOTc1MDE@._V1_SX214_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://www.weekendoffender.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/Robocop-2014-07.jpg</fanart>
<info>In 2028 Detroit, when Alex Murphy - a loving husband, father and good cop - is critically injured in the line of duty, the multinational conglomerate OmniCorp sees their chance for a part-man, part-robot police officer.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Maze Runner (2014)</title>
<link>http://144.76.186.45/r57/5/tyler/movie/TheMazeRunnerDVD-TylerMovieLand.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>http://www.playwatchmovie.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/The-Maze-Runner-2014.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://static.guim.co.uk/sys-images/Guardian/Pix/pictures/2014/10/8/1412778595859/The-Maze-Runner-2014-014.jpg</fanart>
<info>Thomas is deposited in a community of boys after his memory is erased, soon learning they're all trapped in a maze that will require him to join forces with fellow "runners" for a shot at escape.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>I, Frankenstein (2014)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://www.spacemov.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/i-frankenstein-poster_138908704700.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://www.heyuguys.com/images/2014/01/0249204924.jpg</fanart>
<info>Frankenstein's creature finds himself caught in an all-out, centuries old war between two immortal clans.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Interstellar (2014)</title>
<link>http://www.promptfile.com/l/E84F3406C8-B937721520</link>
<thumbnail>http://cdn.screenrant.com/wp-content/uploads/interstellar-poster.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://cdni.condenast.co.uk/1083x658/g_j/Interstellar-02-GQ-30Oct14_pr_b_1083x658.jpg</fanart>
<info>A team of explorers travel through a wormhole in an attempt to ensure humanity's survival.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Pacific Rim (2013)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTY3MTI5NjQ4Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwOTU1OTU0OQ@@._V1_SX500_SY999_.jpg?</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://deltorofilms.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/01/pacificrim_jaegers_wallpaper.jpg</fanart>
<info>As a war between humankind and monstrous sea creatures wages on, a former pilot and a trainee are paired up to drive a seemingly obsolete special weapon in a desperate effort to save the world from the apocalypse.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Ghost in the Shell Arise: Border 2 - Ghost Whisper (2013)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://fr.web.img1.acsta.net/pictures/14/08/25/11/35/504471.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://www.mangauk.com/gallery/albums/album-19/lg/gits_arise_1.jpg</fanart>
<info>(ENG and Jap Sound) Freed of her responsibilities with the 501 Organization, Motoko Kusanagi must now learn how to take orders from Aramaki. Someone hacks the Logicomas, and Batou enlists the help of former army intelligence officer Ishikawa and former air artillery expert Borma. Kusanagi also seeks to enlist ace sniper Saito and undercover cop Paz into the new Public Security Section 9.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Host (2013)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjMwNDg1MTAzNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNTk5ODI3OA@@._V1_SX500_SY999_.jpg?</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://wtfbabe.files.wordpress.com/2013/12/the-host-05-still-wtf-watch-the-film-saint-pauly.jpg</fanart>
<info>When an unseen enemy threatens mankind by taking over their bodies and erasing their memories, Melanie will risk everything to protect the people she cares most about, proving that love can conquer all in a dangerous new world.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>R.I.P.D. (2013)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTM5OTYxNzE5N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDU1MTQ4OQ@@._V1_SX500_SY999_.jpg?</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-iCExHO7Hqmg/UerkmNBQhjI/AAAAAAAABvo/ieHtGqRB0dQ/s1600/RIPD-Screenshot.png</fanart>
<info>A recently slain cop joins a team of undead police officers working for the Rest in Peace Department and tries to find the man who murdered him.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Dark Skies (2013)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTcxNDE1OTgyOF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMTEyMzMxOQ@@._V1_SX500_SY999_.jpg?</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://oyster.ignimgs.com/wordpress/stg.ign.com/2013/02/original1.jpg</fanart>
<info>As the Barret family's peaceful suburban life is rocked by an escalating series of disturbing events, they come to learn that a terrifying and deadly force is after them.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>The World's End (2013)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNzA1MTk1MzY0OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjkzNTUwMDE@._V1_SX500_SY999_.jpg?</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://www.flixist.com/ul/215697-the-worlds-end-simon-pegg-edgar-wright-nick-frost.jpg</fanart>
<info>Five friends who reunite in an attempt to top their epic pub crawl from 20 years earlier unwittingly become humankind's only hope for survival.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Star Trek: Into Darkness (2013)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://www.movierulz.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/Star-Trek-Into-Darkness-2013.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://www.trekmate.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/star-trek-into-darkness-itunes.jpg</fanart>
<info>After the crew of the Enterprise find an unstoppable force of terror from within their own organization, Captain Kirk leads a manhunt to a war-zone world to capture a one-man weapon of mass destruction.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Total Recall (2012)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMzQ2NzYwOTEzMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNjExNTMxOA@@._V1_SX500_SY999_.jpg?</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://www.lastgizmo.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/colin_farrell_in_total_recall-1920x1080.jpg</fanart>
<info>A factory worker, Douglas Quaid, begins to suspect that he is a spy after visiting Rekall - a company that provides its clients with implanted fake memories of a life they would like to have led - goes wrong and he finds himself on the run.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Watch (2012)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjU5MzI1NTk1MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMzk5NzY5Nw@@._V1_SX500_SY999_.jpg?</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://wp.production.patheos.com/blogs/tinseltalk/files/2012/07/The-Watch-01.jpg</fanart>
<info>Four men who form a neighborhood watch group as a way to get out of their day-to-day family routines find themselves defending the Earth from an alien invasion.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Dredd (2012)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BODkyNDQzMzUzOF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwODYyMDEyOA@@._V1_SX500_SY999_.jpg?</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://www.xboxachievements.com/images/news/dredd.jpg</fanart>
<info>In a violent, futuristic city where the police have the authority to act as judge, jury and executioner, a cop teams with a trainee to take down a gang that deals the reality-altering drug, SLO-MO.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Battle Los Angeles (2011)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjA2MjQ2MzMwMV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMjIwODgzNA@@._V1_SX500_SY999_.jpg?</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://orangelegfilms.files.wordpress.com/2011/03/battle-los-angeles-820513167.jpg</fanart>
<info>A squadron of U.S. Marines becomes the last line of defense against a global invasion.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Dead Space: Aftermath (2011)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BOTU4MTQxOTQzNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDY4NTQyNA@@._V1_SX500_SY999_.jpg?</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://www.youngmanblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/02/d5s5s4d.jpg</fanart>
<info>Based on the much-anticipated EA videogame Dead Space 2, Dead Space: Aftermath is a fast-pased, horrifying thrill ride that follows the surviving ship crew members of the USG O'Bannon. The year is 2509 and not only has Earth lost contact with the Ishimura and Isaac Clarke, but also now the USG O'Bannon, the first responder ship sent to rescue them. </info>
</item>

<item>
<title>I Am Number Four (2011)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/6/62/I_Am_Number_Four_Poster.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://cdn.filmschoolrejects.com/images/Teresa-Palmer-in-I-AM-NUMBER-FOUR_4.jpg</fanart>
<info>Aliens and their Guardians are hiding on Earth from intergalactic bounty hunters. They can only be killed in numerical order, and Number Four is next on the list. This is his story.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Limitless (2011)</title>
<link>http://primeshare.tv/download/35F46C86EE</link>
<thumbnail>http://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/olOuaJPYosJGqWhkqdLXZBSN9GX.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://i.imgur.com/jrzb0.jpg</fanart>
<info>With the help of a mysterious pill that enables the user to access 100 percent of his brain abilities, a struggling writer becomes a financial wizard, but it also puts him in a new world with lots of dangers.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Attack the Block (2011)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjAzNjc1MjgzOF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMzE3Njk5NQ@@._V1_SX500_SY999_.jpg?</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://www.aceshowbiz.com/images/still/attack-the-block06.jpg</fanart>
<info>A teen gang in South London defend their block from an alien invasion.</info>
</item>


<item>
<title>Real Steel (2011)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://www.dreamworksstudios.com/files/rs_1sht_payoff-web.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://www.dreamworksstudios.com/files/rs-ff-002.jpg</fanart>
<info>In the near future, robot boxing is a top sport. A struggling promoter feels he's found a champion in a discarded robot.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Repo Men (2010)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjA4MTUxODM0MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDg3MTgwMw@@._V1_SX500_SY999_.jpg?</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://static01.nyt.com/images/2010/03/19/movies/19repospan-1/19repospan-1-articleLarge.jpg</fanart>
<info>Set in the near future when artificial organs can be bought on credit, it revolves around a man who struggles to make the payments on a heart he has purchased. He must therefore go on the run before said ticker is repossessed.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>TRON: Legacy (2010)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/c/c2/Tron_Legacy_poster.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://img2.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20131122033047/disney/images/7/7c/Tron_Legacy_1366x768-1-.jpg</fanart>
<info>The son of a virtual world designer goes looking for his father and ends up inside the digital world that his father designed. He meets his father's corrupted creation and a unique ally who was born inside the digital world.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Daybreakers (2009)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNzg3NDYyMDU4Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwODA5NzA5Mg@@._V1_SX500_SY999_.jpg?</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://www.stfimages.in/images/2013/07/02/oIedW.png</fanart>
<info>In the year 2019, a plague has transformed almost every human into vampires. Faced with a dwindling blood supply, the fractured dominant race plots their survival; meanwhile, a researcher works with a covert band of vamps on a way to save humankind.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Avatar (2009)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://toloka.hurtom.com/photos/10043009261411327_f0_0.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/3/38/Avatarjakeneytiri.jpg</fanart>
<info>A Paraplegic Marine dispatched to the moon Pandora on a unique mission becomes torn between following his orders and protecting the world he feels is his home..</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>I Am Legend (2007)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>https://encrypted-tbn1.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcTCfvUR5UP8PvecIXGHlVmRBPiuhj1CqnRxSUb-vEpmqzlyqFbS</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://cykomoviesngames.files.wordpress.com/2012/03/i_am_legend2.jpg</fanart>
<info>Years after a plague kills most of humanity and transforms the rest into monsters, the sole survivor in New York City struggles valiantly to find a cure.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Æon Flux (2005)</title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail>http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-DFkHO_-1zdk/UqIOVxgt2GI/AAAAAAAAQnQ/OL3dmocRN2Q/s1600/2005+AEon+Flux+Movie+Watch+Online+Free+In+Hindi+and+Urdu.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://images1.fanpop.com/images/photos/1600000/-on-flux-charlize-theron-1693460-1024-768.jpg</fanart>
<info>Aeon Flux is a mysterious assassin working for the Monicans, a group of rebels trying to overthrow the government. When she is a sent on a mission to kill the Chairman, a whole new mystery is found.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Starship Troopers (1997)</title>
<link>http://www.nowvideo.sx/video/pvar5p3enbg5c</link>
<thumbnail>https://encrypted-tbn1.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcTtABU2DjeojT62uMN_Aj02BivYT5Z0FG9g_R1RJlg--Xxrv-m7</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://filmtipps.tv/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/Starship-Troopers1.jpg</fanart>
<info>Humans in a fascistic, militaristic future do battle with giant alien bugs in a fight for survival.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title></title>
<link></link>
<thumbnail></thumbnail>
<fanart></fanart>
<info></info>
</item>
